Contact

Perak, Malaysia +601133600120 (Mobile) nivesh48@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nivesh-gadipudi-5304b1a7 (LinkedIn) github.com/nivesh48 (Other) www.ieeeutp.org/ (Company)

Top Skills

Control Engineering Machine Vision Machine Learning

Certifications

Summer School on Al
Neural Networks and Deep Learning
FUNDAMENTALS OF
ACCELERATED COMPUTING
WITH CUDA C/C++

Mathematics for Machine Learning: Linear Algebra

3D Vision Summer School

Nivesh Gadipudi

Computer Vision, and Deep Learning Engineer | Ex-Vimaan | Ex-TCS Research

Andhra Pradesh, India

Summary

I work on robotic perception algorithms. I am primarily interested in 3D reconstruction. My secondary interests are in research on algorithms those use information from scene for decision-making like segmentation, detection, and classification

A huge fan of the book "Multiple View Geometry in Computer Vision"

Areas of interest: Computer Vision, 3D Vision, Multi-view Geometry, Differential Geometry, and Deep Learning

Topics of interest: Robust Estimators, Feature Extraction and Matching, Visual Odometry, Visual SLAM, and Camera Pose Estimation

Experience

Trinity College Dublin
Postdoctoral Researcher
September 2023 - Present (1 month)
Dublin, County Dublin, Ireland

Vimaan

Computer Vision Engineer January 2023 - August 2023 (8 months) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Tata Consultancy Services TCS Research - Research Internship February 2022 - December 2022 (11 months)

India

IEEE Universiti Teknologi PETRONAS (UTP) Student Branch Chairperson

February 2020 - January 2022 (2 years)

Perak, Malaysia

Universiti Teknologi PETRONAS Research Intern February 2018 - September 2018 (8 months) Malaysia

Education

Universiti Teknologi PETRONAS

Doctor of Philosophy - PhD, Electrical and Electronics Engineering · (April 2019 - April 2023)

Vellore Institute of Technology

Master of Technology - MTech, Mechatronics · (2016 - 2018)

RMK ENGINEERING COLLEGE, CHENNAI

Bachelor's degree, Mechanical Engineering · (2012 - 2016)